<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OneNote REST API Explorer</string>
    <string name="title_snippet_detail">Snippet Detail</string>
    <string name="beta">BETA</string>
    <string name="v1_0">v1.0</string>
    <string name="run">Run</string>
    <string name="req_url">Request URL</string>
    <string name="req_headers">Request Headers</string>
    <string name="req_body">Request Body</string>
    <string name="response">Response</string>
    <string name="response_headers">Response Headers</string>
    <string name="response_body">Response Body</string>
    <string name="docs"><u>Documentation</u></string>
    <string name="status_code">HTTP Status Code</string>
    <string name="msa_hint">Sign in with the account you use for OneDrive, Xbox Live, Outlook.com, or other Microsoft services. Currently, requests from an MSA account are not supported. Support is upcoming.</string>
    <string name="o365_hint">Sign in with the account provided by your work or school to use with Office 365 or other Microsoft services</string>
    <string name="org_acct">Organizational Account</string>
    <string name="microsoft_acct">Microsoft Account</string>
    <string name="launch_onenote">Open in OneNote</string>
    <string name="launch_browser">Open in browser</string>
    <string name="quick_links">Quick Links</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="clippy">copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="token_err_title">Failed to acquire api token</string>
    <string name="token_err_msg">Office 365 has either failed to refresh the access token or is unavailable. To view the extended stacktrace, click \'Dismiss\' then view the Response Body section</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="offline_access_permission">Allows the app to read and update user data, even when they are not currently using the app.</string>
    <string name="open_id">Allows users to sign in to the app with their work or school accounts and allows the app to see basic user profile information.</string>
    <string name="NotesReadWriteAll">Allows the app to read and write the contents of all notebooks and sections that the signed-in user can access.  It cannot access password protected sections.</string>
    <string name="NotesReadWrite">Allows the app to read the titles of notebooks and sections, read all pages, write all pages and create new pages on behalf of the signed-in user.  It cannot access password protected sections.</string>
    <string name="unavailable">unavailable</string>
    <string name="err_setup">Error preparing snippet</string>
    <string name="err_setup_msg">This snippet requires a notebook, section, group, or page before it will run. For example if you are deleting a page, you must first have a page to delete. Check that the appropriate item exists before running this snippet.</string>
    <string name="et_hint">&lt;Your text here&gt;</string>
    <string name="warning_clientid_redirecturi_incorrect">The client ID or redirect URI is not valid. Enter a valid client ID and redirect URI in the ServiceConstants.java file and run again</string>
    <string name="signin_err">An error signing in has occurred. Check LogCat for details.</string>
</resources>
